(忆往昔)
我曾经功成名就
I was on the fast track once.
一直都是每月最佳员工
Employee of the month every month -- forever.
然后他们让我解决你们的问题
And then they assigned me you.
我竟然不能解决
I can't close the deal
几个穿着法兰绒的可怜虫
on a couple of pathetic, flannel-wearing maggots?
大家都嘲笑我
Everybody's laughing at me.
我们是约翰·温彻斯特的儿子
We're John Winchester's sons.
我还有哥哥
I've got brothers?
亚当不该受这诅咒
Adam doesn't have to be cursed.
他是温彻斯特家的人  他已经被诅咒了
He's a Winchester. He's already cursed.
你不是亚当  一直就不是
You're not Adam. You've never been Adam.
你是食尸鬼
You're a ghoul.
你杀不死路西法  你在逐渐失去对自己
You can't kill the devil, and you're losing faith
和你弟弟的信心
in yourself, your brother.
上帝是你最后的希望
God was your last hope.
你不是要去做蠢事吧
Are you gonna do something stupid?
比如说
Like what?
比如米迦勒版迪恩
Like Michael stupid.
不管你打算干什么  别去
Whatever you're thinking of doing, don't do it.
我必须去
I have to.
(如今)
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
被炒鱿鱼了
Pink-slipped?
那么明显哈
That obvious, huh?
同病相怜
Takes one to know one.
外包惹的祸
"Outsourcing."
你犯了何种反人类罪行
What was your crime against humanity?
千年项目
Deal of the millennium.
最最简单的一个同意都要不到
Couldn't even get the one simple "Yes" I needed.
最低盈利要求总得达到  是吧
Got to nail that bottom line, right?
了解
Hear that.
上面那些人唯一关心的就是
All they care about upstairs, ain't it?
结果  结果  结果
Results, results, results.
他们不了解
They don't know.
他们从不下到底层  到这滩烂泥里
They're not down on the ground, in the mud,
跟你们这些猪一样肮脏的人类打交道
nose to nose with all you pig-filthy humans.
我说得不对吗
Am I right?
太对了  肮脏的什么
Absolutely -- filthy what?
我说  他们的义气都哪儿去了
I mean, whatever happened to personal loyalty?
我为他们工作多久了
How long have I worked for these guys?
五千年  六千年
Five millennia? Six?
感觉确实那么久
Seems like it, don't it?
说得对  就是这样
Damn straight, it does.
再来两杯
Two more.
撒迦
Zach.
斯图尔特
Stuart.
你下一步想怎么办  斯图尔特
What are you gonn do next, Stuart?
还没想好
Hell, I don't know.
或许做些与网略有关的工作
Maybe something to do with the Internet.
是嘛
Yeah?
地震了
Whoa. Earthquake?
不是
No.
是我老板
My boss.
来吧
Go ahead.
给我个了断
Get it over with.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
等等
Wait
什么
What?
是的  任何事情  当然
Yes! Anything. Of course.
只要让我回去  我不会让你失望的
Just -- just put me back in. You won't regret it.
谢谢
Thank you.
Thank you!
小子们  爷又上岗了
Back in business, boys!
[邪恶力量 第5季第18集]
(罗伯特·辛格  收)
给别人寄糖呢吗
Sending someone a candygram?
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
你要去自杀  是不是
You're gonna kill yourself, right?
告别之旅的行程很容易猜得到
It's not too hard to figure out the stops on the farewell tour.
莉莎过得怎么样
How's Lisa doing, anyway?
我没想去自杀
I'm not gonna kill myself.
是吗
No?
这么说米迦勒不会拿你当牵线木偶来使
So, Michael's not about to make you his muppet?
你到底想怎样  就这样结束了吗
What the hell, man? This is how it ends?
你就  甩手不干了
You just... Walk out?
我猜是的
Yeah, I guess.
你怎么可以这样
How could you do that?
我怎么可以
How could I?
一直都在逃避的是你
All you've ever done is run away!
我错了  每一次的逃避都是错误的
And I was wrong every single time I did.
求你了
Just...  Please...
先别放弃
Not now.
鲍比在研究对策
Bobby is working on something.
是吗  什么对策
Oh, really? What?
根本没有对策  你心里清楚
You got nothing, and you know it.
你知道我一定要阻止你
You know I have to stop you.
好啊  你放马过来吧
Yeah, well, you can try.
不过别忘了
But just remember,
这次可没有恶魔血助你一臂之力了
you're not all hopped up on demon blood this time.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
可我带了帮手
But I brought help.
好  真好  太好了
Yeah, no, this is good, really.
八个月来各种瞎忙活  一无所获
Eight months of turned pages and screwed pooches,
可是今天  一夜之间就会发生奇迹
But tonight... tonight's when the magic happens.
别捣乱
You ain't helping.
那你怎么还不让我滚蛋
Yeah, well, why don't you let me get out of your hair, then?
你犯什么病了
What the hell happened to you?
犯了认清现实的病
Reality happened.
使用原子弹是唯一的办法
Nuclear's the only option we have left.
米迦勒能干掉路西法  救下很多人
Michael can ice the devil, save a boatload of people.
但不是所有人
But not all of them.
我们必须找其他办法
We got to think of something else.
你说着倒是容易
Yeah, well, that's easy for you to say,
如果路西法把地球毁了
but if Lucifer burns this mother down
而我本可以改变这一切
and I could have done something about it,
猜猜怎么着  都是我的错
guess what -- that's on me.
你不能就此放弃  孩子
You can't give up, son.
你不是我父亲
You're not my father.
更无法理解我的立场
And you ain't in my shoes.
那是什么
What is that?
是我想用来射穿自己脑袋的子弹
That's the round I mean to put through my skull.
每天早上  我都会看着它
Every morning, I look at it,
我在想
and I think...
或许今天就该是我瞑目之日了
"Maybe today's the day I flip the lights out."
但我没有那么做
But I don't do it.
我绝不会那么做
I never do it.
知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为我答应过你们  我不会放弃
Because I promised you I wouldn't give up!
卡西  你还好吗
Cass, you okay?
不好
No.
怎么了
What's wrong?
有点不对劲
Something's happening.
哪里
Where?
麻烦让让  我要拿瓶酒
I'm gonna get a beer. Do you mind?
来帮忙
Help.
孩子们
Boys!
这是谁
Who is it?
我们的弟弟
That's our brother.
等等  你们的弟弟  亚当
Wait a minute. Your brother? Adam?
卡西  怎么回事
Cass, what the hell?
天使干的
Angels.
天使  为什么
Angels? Why?
我现在只确定一件事
I know one thing for sure.
就是我们得把他藏起来
We need to hide him now.
-我在哪  - 没事了
- Where am I? - It's okay.
放松点  你安全了
Just relax. You're safe.
你们又是谁
Who the hell are you?
你可能会觉得有点
You're gonna find this a little --
是非常疯狂  但事实上咱们是兄弟
a lot crazy, but we're actually your brothers.
这是真的
It's the truth.
约翰·温彻斯特也是我们的父亲
John Winchester was our father, too.
瞧  我是萨姆
See, I'm Sam.
嗯  那这位就是迪恩了
Yeah, and I'm sure that's Dean.
我知道你们是谁
I know who you are.
-怎么会  - 他们让我警惕你们
- How? - They warned me about you.
-谁说的  - 天使
- Who did? - The angels.
撒迦利亚在哪儿
Now, where the hell is Zachariah?!
那么  和我们说说这整件事吧
So, why don't you just tell us everything?
从最开始说起
Start from the beginning.
我那时死了  然后去了天堂
Well, I was dead and in heaven...
只不过  那儿看起来像是我的舞会
...Except it -- it, uh, kind of looked like my prom.
我和一个女孩子打得火热
And I was making out with this girl.
她叫作克莉丝汀·米基
Her -- her name was Kristin McGee.
的确  这听起来就像天堂
Yeah, that sounds like heaven.
你上了三垒没
Did you get to third base?
接  接着说
Just, uh...Just keep going.
这些天使  就凭空出现了
Well, these -- these angels, they popped out of nowhere,
然后告诉我  我是被选中的
and they tell me that I-I'm chosen.
做什么
For what?
拯救世界
To save the world.
你打算怎么救
How you gonna do that?
我和什么大天使会杀死路西法
Oh, me and some archangel are gonna kill the devil.
哪个大天使
What archangel?
米迦勒
Michael.
我是他的利剑或皮囊  或者什么其他的
I'm his, uh, sword or vessel or something.
我说不清
I don't know
这怎么可能
well, that's insane.
不一定
Not necessarily.
此话怎讲
How do you mean?
或许他们放弃你了  迪恩
Maybe they're moving on from you, Dean.
这说不通啊
That doesn't make sense.
他具有约翰·温彻斯特的血统
He's John Winchester's bloodline,
也是萨姆的兄弟
Sam's brother.
或许不尽完美  但也不无可能
It's not perfect, but it's possible.
你在开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
他们为什么要这么做
Why would they do this?
或许他们绝望了
Maybe they're desperate.
或许他们高估了迪恩
Maybe they've wrongly assumed
以为他勇敢到能经受住他们的压力
Dean would be brave enough to withstand them.
够了  卡西  来虐我啊
All right, you know what? Blow me, Cass.
听着  这不可能
Look. No way.
发生了这么多事之后
After everything that's happened
还有那关于命运的鬼话
All that crap about destiny,
突然间天使就有了B计划
suddenly the angels have a plan "B"?
有谁会觉得这正常吗
Does that smell right to anybody?
听着  家人重聚真令人感动
You know, this has been a really moving family reunion,
不过  我还有事  就
but, uh, I got a thing, so --
什么  不 不 不  坐下
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, no. Sit down.
认真听着  好吗
Just listen, okay?
拜托了
Please.
难以置信
It's unbelievable.
现在  亚当
Now, Adam...
天使骗了你
the angels are lying to you.
他们满嘴跑火车
They're full of crap.
可惜我不这么想
Yeah, I don't think so.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why not?
因为他们是天使啊
Um, 'cause they're angels.
他们告诉你他们要烧毁半个星球了吗
They tell you they were gonna roast half the planet?
他们说了这会是惊险的一战
They said the fight might get pretty hairy,
但对方是路西法  对吧
But it is the devil, right?
所以我们必须制止他
So, we got to stop him.
的确  但是还有其他办法
Yeah, but there's another way.
很好  是什么呢
Great. What is it?
我们的目标是  用爱拯救地球
Well, we're working on the power of love.
-进展如何  - 不太顺哦
- How's that going? - Not good.
听着  亚当
look, Adam...
俗话说知人知面不知心  我明白
You don't know me from a hole in the wall, I know,
但我求你
But I'm begging you.
拜托了  信任我吧
Please, just trust me.
给我点时间
Give me some time.
凭什么
Give me one good reason.
我们是血亲
Because we're blood.
你没资格跟我说这个
You got no right to say that to me.
你依然是约翰的孩子
You're still John's boy.
不  约翰·温切斯特是个
No, John Winchester was some guy
每年带我看一场棒球赛的家伙
who took me to a baseball game once a year.
我没有爸爸
I didn't have a dad.
我们可能是血亲  但我们不是家人
So, we may be blood, but we are not family.
我妈才是我家人
My mom is my family,
我好好尽我本分  就能再次见到她
and if I do my job, I get to see her again.
无意冒犯  但让我上心的人是她
So, no offense, but she's the one I give a rat's ass about,
而不是你们
not you.
也对
Fair enough.
但要是老爸给过你快乐的回忆
But if you have one good memory of dad,
只有一次都好
just one.
就给我们多一点点时间
Then you'll give us a little more time.
拜托了
Please.
去哪呢
Going somewhere?
出去弄点啤酒
Out for a...Beer.
很好  我们有啤酒  坐下吧
Great. We got beer. Have a seat.
很好
Great.
你唱这么一出天真无邪的哥俩好的戏
You know, you pitch this whole dewy-eyed bromance thing,
实际上是想盯紧我吧
but the truth is, I'm on lockdown, aren't I?
亚当
Adam...
你可能不信
...you may not believe it,
但老爸那样做是想保护你
but dad was trying to protect you,
为了不把你卷进来
keeping you from all this.
是啊  我想把我吞下去的那只怪物
Yeah, well, I guess the monster that ate me
没接到这消息
didn't get that memo.
你都记得
You remember that?
那是啊
Oh, yeah.
还是那句  相信我
Still, trust me,
比一年见一次老爸还糟糕的事情
The one thing worse than seeing dad once a year
就是天天见他
was seeing him all year.
你还真是满嘴跑大车
Do you know how full of crap you are?
- 什么  - 真的
- What?  - Really.
这个家只有我和我妈  仅此而已
You see, it was me, and it was my mom, that's it.
她在医院上夜班
She worked the graveyard shift at the hospital.
我自己做饭  自己睡觉
I cooked my own dinners. I put myself to bed.
关于我们的爸爸  你想怎么评论都行
So, you can say whatever you want about our dad,
但事实是  和爸爸相处是我梦寐以求的
but the truth is, I would have taken anything.
明白了吗
All right?
要是我们知道我们还有个兄弟
Look, if we had known we had a brother --
可你们不知道
Well, you didn't, so...
我们会找到你的
...we would have found you.
我无法改变过去
Look, I can't change the past.
我希望我能
I wish I could.
但从今以后
But from here on out --
又怎样
What?
大家钻进车里
We gonna hop in the family truckster?
然后一起到沃尔玛去血拼吗
Pop on down to Wally world?
我跟你说
Tell you one thing...
这样的态度
attitude like that,
实在是太适合这里了
you'd fit right in around here.
卡西  不是我说啊
Well, Cass, not for nothing,
不过上一个用这种小眼神儿看我的人
but the last person who looked at me like that...
我们嘿咻了
I got laid.
不如你去看着亚当吧
Uh, why don't you, uh, go keep an eye on Adam?
有必要吗
Is this really necessary?
我们都很忙  迪恩
Well I mean, we got our hands full, Dean --
满屋子人都时刻准备着
a houseful of flight risks.
我不会让他那么做的
I'm not letting him do it.
谁  亚当吗  我也不会
Who, Adam? No, I'm -- I'm not, either.
不  你不明白我的意思
No, you're not getting me.
不不不  我完全了解
Oh, no, no, I "Get" You perfectly.
但我也不会让你这么做的
But I'm not letting you do it, either.
我不会让那孩子替我受罪的
That kid's not taking a bullet for me.
- 迪恩  - 说真的
- Dean  - I'm serious.
想想看  有多少人
I mean, think about how many people
是被我们害死的  萨姆
we've gotten killed, Sam.
妈  爸
Mom, dad...
杰丝  乔  埃伦
Jess, Jo, Ellen.
还要继续数吗
Should I keep going?
并不是我们亲手杀了他们
It's not like we pulled the trigger.
我们也可能丢了小命的
We might as well have.
我累了  兄弟
I'm tired, man.
我不想再和本性抗争了
I'm tired of fighting who I'm supposed to be.
麻烦你能不能消停个半秒钟
Well, do you think maybe you could take a half a second
别再试着为改变现状而自我牺牲如何
and stop trying to sacrifice yourself for a change?
说不定我们能一直在一起呢
Maybe we could actually stick together?
我可不觉得
I don't think so.
为什么
Why not?
迪恩  真的
Dean, seriously.
告诉我吧  我想知道
Tell me. I-I want to know.
我只是
I just...
我  我无法相信
I-I don't believe.
不信什么
In what?
不信你
In you.
我不
I mean, I don't...
我不知道他们是会用恶魔血引诱你
I don't know whether it's gonna be demon blood
还是让另一个恶魔小妞勾引你
or some other demon chick or what, but...
但我知道他们会设法让你魔化
...I do know they're gonna find a way to turn you.
你是说我不够坚强吗
So, you're saying I'm not strong enough.
你易怒  自以为是
You're angry, you're self-righteous.
路西法会占有你的身体的  兄弟
Lucifer's gonna wear you to the prom, man.
只是时间问题罢了
It's just a matter of time.
别这么跟我说话
Don't say that to me.
全天下人里
Not you...
只有你不行
of all people.
我也不想
I don't want to.
但这是事实
But it's the truth.
等到撒旦控制了你的身体
And when Satan takes you over,
必须有人出来和它战斗
there's got to be somebody there to fight him,
而那个孩子可做不到
and it ain't gonna be that kid.
所以  只有我来挺身而出
So, it's got to be me.
他怎么样
How's he doing?
你呢
How're you doing?
迪恩
Dean?
卡西
Cass.
卡西哪去了
Where's Cass?
被传送到天边了[出自《绿野仙踪》]
Blown to O.Z.
我去把迪恩找回来
Look, I'll get Dean.
他应该还没走太远
He couldn't have gone too far.
-你在这看着亚当  - 怎么看着
- Just watch Adam.  - How?
你又不是不知道  他稍占点身高优势
You may have noticed, he's got a slight height advantage.
那就把他绑在你轮椅上  随便你
Then cuff him to your chair. I don't know.
看住他就行
Just watch him.
你妈妈不会来了
Your mom's not coming, you know.
就是这个公园吗
This is the park
你妈妈休息时常带你来玩
where your mom took you on her day off, right?
她现在还不会来
She's not coming -- not yet.
但她很快就会来
But she will...soon.
你是撒迦利亚吧
You're Zachariah, right?
正是
I am.
你现在的所在地可不对  孩子
You weren't where you were supposed to be, kid.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我们也无法找到你的确切位置
Can't quite zero in on you, either.
我就大胆猜猜吧
So, let me take a wild guess.
你跟萨姆和迪恩在一起吧
You're with Sam and Dean?
对
Yeah.
我们之前不也说过他们的事了吗
Didn't we tell you about them?
你也知道他们不可信
So, you know you can't trust them, right?
要知道那对兄弟的关系不正常
You know Sam and Dean Winchester are psychologically,
谁少了谁都要死要活
irrationally, erotically codependent
就差没乱伦了
on each other, right?
我也搞不清楚
I don't know.
他们跟我讲了点你的事
They said a few things about you.
是吗
Really?
相信我  孩子  等到大难临头
Trust me, kid, when the heat gets hot,
他们才不会为你考虑
they're not gonna give a flying crap about you.
他们宁可给彼此弄点甜培根
Hell, they'd rather save each other's sweet bacon
都不会去拯救世界
than save the planet.
他们不是你的家人
They're not your family.
明白吗
Understand?
现在呢
Now...
你还想再见到你妈妈吗
you want to see your mom again or not?
末日就在眼前
The end is nigh!
天启已经降临
The Apocalypse is upon us!
天使们跟我交流
The angels talk to me,
他们要我向你们传达这消息
and they asked me to talk to you!
-天启  - 喂
- The Apocalypse --  - Hey!
我是迪恩·温彻斯特  认识吗
I'm Dean Winchester. Do you know who I am?
老天啊
Dear God.
看来你是认识了
I'll take that as a yes.
告诉你那帮天使朋友
Listen, I need you to pray to your angel buddies
我就在这里
and let them know that I'm here.
吾父在上
Our father, who art in heaven,
愿汝名被尊为圣
hallowed be thy name.
你祷告太大声了
You pray too loud.
你这是干什么  疯了吗
What, are you crazy?!
我为了你而堕天  你就这么回报我吗?!
I rebelled for this?!
事到如今  你才想到要向他们妥协?!
So that you could surrender to them?
卡西  住手
Cass! Please!
我为你付出了一切
I gave everything for you.
到头来  我换来什么?!
And this is what you give to me.
动手吧
Do it.
快动手啊
Just do it!
鲍比  亚当不见了是啥意思
Bobby, what do you mean, "Adam is gone"?
难道我说的是鸟语吗
Should I say it in Spanish?
他怎么会消失的
He's gone how?
你到底在搞什么  鲍比
What the hell, Bobby?!
小子  和我说话小心点
Watch your tone, boy
他前一刻还在我面前
He was right in front of me,
后一秒就凭空消失了
and he disappeared into thin air.
因为天使带走了他
Because the angels took him.
他这又是怎么了
What the hell happened to him?
是我打的
Me.
你说天使带走了亚当是什么意思
What do you mean, the angels took Adam?
你不是在他的肋骨上刻了咒吗
You branded his ribs, didn't you?
是的  肯定是亚当提示了他们
Yes. Adam must have tipped them.
-怎么提示  - 我也不知道
- How?  - I don't know.
可能是在梦里吧
Maybe in a dream.
那他们会把他带去哪里
Well, where would they have taken him?
看来你和你哥哥口味相同啊
I see you and your brother share the same refined palate.
那么
So, uh...
咱们准备好了吗
we ready?
准备什么
For what?
什么意思  为了米迦勒
What do you mean, for what? For Michael.
对哦
Right.
这件事
About that...
我知道这绝不轻松  但是我恐怕
Look, this is never easy, but I'm afraid...
你的职责到此就不得不告一段落了
we've had to terminate your position at this time.
你说什么
Excuse me?
别误会我
Hey, don't get me wrong,
你辛苦出了很多力  真的  干得不错
you've been a hell of a sport, really -- good stuff.
但问题是
But the thing is,
你更像是个湿漉漉的小诱饵
you're not so much the "Chosen one" as you are...
而并非那个被选定的人
a clammy scrap of bait.
但你以前的话又是怎么回事
No, but what about the stuff that you said?
我应该和恶魔战斗
I'm suposed to fight th devil.
就你吗  省省吧
Mm, not so much.
这算是个安慰吧
Hey, if it's any consolation,
那个我们想要的人
You happen to be the illegitimate half brother
你正好是他的半个私生兄弟
Of the guy we do care about.
这还算不错吧
That's not bad, is it?
这么说  是你骗我
So, you lied...
你所说的一切都是在骗我
About everything.
我们没有骗你
We didn't lie.
只是隐瞒了部分真相  以便操控你
We just avoided certain truths to manipulate you.
你这个混蛋
Oh, you son of a bitch.
你以为我好受吗
Hey, how do you think I feel?
我可是得忍受你
I'm the one that's got to put up
那一脸的呆滞木讷相啊
with that dumb, slack-jawed look on your face.
孩子  我们没得选
Kid, we didn't have a choice.
温彻斯特家有个致命弱点
The winchesters got one blind spot,
就是家人
And it's family.
萨姆和迪恩得摒弃前嫌
See, Sam and Dean, they're gonna put aside their differences,
前来救你
And they're gonna come get you,
这样就会把迪恩引到这里
And that is gonna put Dean right...Here --
如此一来  便正合我意
Right where I need him.
孩子  今夜是关键的一夜
This is the night, kid!
是属于我们的夜晚
Our night.
米迦勒早就预见到了
Michael's seen it.
一切终于步上正轨
The tumblers finally click into place,
这都归功于你
And it's all because of you.
还有我  但是谁会管这个呢
And me. But who's keeping score?
想得美  我不会让你得逞
Yeah, I'm not gonna let you do this.
冷静点  软木头  坐下
Cool your jets, corky. Sit down.
我们一起做这件事
We're doing it together.
你还是可以拿到离职金
Plus, you still get your severance.
你仍可以见到你妈妈  好吗
You still get to see your mom, okay?
我凭什么相信你
Why should I believe you?
告诉你吧
You know what?
我之前一直太客气了
I keep hearing this.
看来老子得来点硬的才行
But what I want to be hearing is this.
这样才对
That's better.
感觉怎样
How you feeling?
友情提醒
Word to the wise...
惹怒天然呆天使的下场可不好受
Don't piss off the nerd angels.
现在什么情况
So, how's it going?
亚当不见了
Adam's gone.
天使带走了他
The agels have him.
带去哪儿了
Where?
就是他们之前带你去的那间屋子
The room where they took you.
你确定吗
You sure?
卡西去查过了
Cass did a recon.
还有呢
And?
那里满是天堂的走狗
And the place is crawling with mooks --
满脸假仁假义  口蜜腹剑的天使混蛋
pretty much a no-shot-in-hell, hail-mary kind of thing.
还是老样子
Ah, so the usual.
你准备怎么做
What are you gonna do?
首先
For starters...
我和你一起去
I'm bringing you with.
什么
Excuse me?
他们数量太多
There are too many of them.
单打独斗可不行
We can't do it alone,
再说这镇上也只有你能行
And, uh, you're pretty much the only game in town.
你确定不会后悔吗
Isn't that a bad idea?
卡西和鲍比不认同我
Cass and Bobby think so.
但我有我的想法
I'm not so sure.
听他们的没错
Well, they're right.
这要不是个圈套
Because either it's a trap
把我引过去  好逼我就范
To get me there, to make me say yes,
就算不是圈套  不管怎样  我都会答应他们
Or it's not a trap I'm gonna say yes anyway.
我肯定会  事先警告你
And I will. I'll do it -- fair warning.
不  你不会
No, you won't.
到了关键时刻  你就会做出正确决定
When push shoves, you'll make the right call.
要是换作是我
You know, if tables were turned...
我会让你烂在这地下室里
I'd let you rot in here.
一点也没错  我做得出来
Hell, I have let you rot in here.
这样啊
Yeah, well...
可能我比较笨吧
I guess I'm not that smart.
我不懂  萨姆  你为什么这么做
I-I don't get it. Sam, why are you doing this?
因为
Because...
你依然是我哥
...You're still my Big Brother.
我们到底在哪
Where the hell are we?
加州范奈司市
Van Nuys, California.
那个靓屋在哪儿
Where's the beautiful room
就在这里
In there.
那间靓屋居然在加州范奈斯市的
The beautiful room is in an abandoned muffler factory
一座废弃的消音器工厂
In Van Nuys, California?
那你觉得是在哪儿
Where'd you think it was?
不知道  木星?
I-I don't know. Jupiter?
丁点儿家伙上?  反正不是范奈司市
A blade of grass? Not van nuys.
我还是不懂  为什么你不能带着亚当
Tell me again why you don't just grab Adam
直接瞬间转移离开那鬼地方
and shazam the hell out of there.
因为那里至少有5个天使
Because there are at least five angels in there.
-又怎样  你很快啊  - 他们更快
- So? You're fast. - They're faster.
我会搞定他们
I'll clear them out.
你俩去救那个男孩
You two grab the boy.
这是我们唯一的机会
This is our only chance.
慢着  你要对付5个天使吗
Whoa, wait. You're gonna take on five angels?
是的
Yes.
这不是找死吗
Isn't that suicide?
算是吧
Maybe it is.
总比看着你妥协来得强
But then I won't have to watch you fail.
不好意思  迪恩
I'm sorry, Dean.
我可不像萨姆那样有信心
I don't have the same faith in you that Sam does.
你拿那个干什么
What the hell are you gonna do with that?
你们还等什么
What are you waiting for?
上啊
Come on.
亚当
Adam, hey. Hey.
你们为了我而来
You came for me.
你是我们的家人
You're family.
迪恩  这是个陷阱
Dean, it's a trap.
我知道
I figured.
得了  迪恩  你也太天真了吧
Dean, please. Did you really think it would be that easy?
你说呢
Did you?
萨姆
Sam!
你知道我吃那么多堑长了什么智吗
You know what I've learned from this experience, Dean?
耐心可贵
Patience.
亚当
Adam?
放了他  你这混蛋
Let him go, you son of a bitch.
我本以为自己肯定被抛弃了
I mean, I thought I was downsized for sure,
用你们的话说  叫解雇
and for us, a firing -- pretty damn literal.
但我早该相信我的头儿
But I should have trusted the boss man.
一切都在他的意料之中
It's all playing out like he said...
你  我  还有你那吐血的兄弟们
you, me, your hemorrhaging brothers.
你终于准备好了吧
You're finally ready, right?
你没有其他选择
You know there's no other choice.
从来就没有
There's never been a choice.
放过他们  快住手
Stop it. Stop it right now!
用什么来交换呢
In exchange for what?
该死的  撒迦利亚
Damn it, Zachariah.
别伤害他们  求你了
Stop it, please.
我答应
I'll do it.
不好意思  你说什么
I'm sorry. What was that?
好吧  我答应
Okay, yes.
我答应米迦勒
The answer is yes.
迪恩
Dean!
你没听到吗
Do you hear me?
把米迦勒叫来  你这混蛋
Call Michael down, you bastard!
我怎么知道你有没有骗我
How do I know you're not lying?
我看起来像骗人吗
Do I look like I'm lying?
他即将莅临
He's coming.
当然  我还有些条件
Of course, I have a few conditions.
什么
What?
在我答应之前  你要保证
A few people whose safety you have to guarantee
这些人的安全
before I say yes.
当然可以  哪些人  你说
Sure, fine. Make a list.
但是首先
But most of all...
除非米迦勒灭了你  不然他休想占有我
...Michael can't have me until he disintegrates you.
你什么意思
What did you say?
我是说
I said...
米迦勒要想得到我这身臭皮囊
before Michael gets one piece of this sweet ass...
他得先把你化为灰烬
he has to turn you into a piece of charcoal.
你真以为米迦勒会那样做吗
You really think Michael's gonna go for that?
现在孰轻孰重  他还不知道吗
Who's more important to him now?
是你
You...
还是我
or me?
你给我听着
You listen to me.
你只不过是个小角色  不值一提
You are nothing but a maggot inside a worm's ass.
是我把你交给米迦勒
Do you know who I am...
我对他而言意义重大
after I deliver you to Michael?
还不是炮灰一个
Expendable.
米迦勒不可能杀我
Michael's not gonna kill me.
他可能不会
Maybe not.
但我会
But I am.
-你自己能走吗  - 能
- Can you walk? - Yeah.
好的  快走
Okay, come on.
快点  出来
Come on, move it!
不
No!
迪恩  救命
Dean! Help!
谁来救救我
Could anyone help me?
迪恩  救我出去
Dean, help!
迪恩
Dean!
坚持住  我会救你出来
Hold on I'll get you out.
挺住
Please Hold on.
亚当  听见了吗
Adam, can you hear me?
亚当
Adam?
亚当没事吧
You think Adam's okay?
拿不准
Doubt it.
也不知道卡西怎么样了
Cass either.
但是我们会找到他们
But we'll get 'em.
然后呢
So?
然后怎么样
"So" what?
我看到你的眼神
I saw your eyes.
刚刚在那儿  你是真想答应
You were totally rockin' the yes back there.
你为什么改变主意
So, what changed your mind?
想听真话吗
Honestly?
还不是这一堆破事儿
The damndest thing.
世界末日来临
I mean, the world's ending,
我们被压得不堪重负
The walls are coming down on us,
回想起来  我脑海里唯一的想法就是
and I look over to you and all I can think about is
还不是某个蠢材把我拖下水
"This stupid son of a bitch brought me here."
但是我不想让你失望
I just didn't want to let you down.
你没有让我失望
You didn't.
就差一点
You almost did.
幸好你悬崖勒马
But you didn't.
我应该向你道歉
I owe you an apology.
不  老哥  不用
No, man. No, you don't.
让我说完
Just...let me say this.
不知道弟控是不是都这样
I don't know if it's being a big brother or what,
但对我而言
but, to me,
你一直是个流鼻涕的小孩
You've always been this snot-nosed kid
需要我管东管西
that I've had to keep on the straight and narrow.
但是现在我们都知道你已经长大了
I think we both know that that's not you anymore.
该死  你是长大了  懂得信任我
I mean, hell, if you're grown-up enough to find faith in me...
至少我应该投桃报李吧
the least I can do is return the favor.
所以  去他妈的命运使然
So, screw destiny right in the face.
我们用我们的方式  和他们斗争
I say we take the fight to them, do it our way.
听起来不错
Sounds good.